globalinteractive.com 2008-12-17

# Global Interactive - Your site representation company with a wider reach!

  |   
**PRIVACY POLICY**

**GLOBAL INTERACTIVE, LLC** has created this statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to protecting your privacy. This statement discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for Global Interactive. 
  1. **Cookies**  
Global Interactive may employ cookies to improve the web user's online experience. A "cookie" is a small file that is placed on web user's computer hard drive by the web browser. Cookies are used to regulate the ad delivery to the user’s browser and limit the display of single or similar ad materials per session.
  2. **Web users**  
No personally identifiable web user information (i.e. address, street address, phone number or email) is collected, distributed or sold by Global Interactive. General web user information is automatically logged during the ad-serving process. Certain Web user data collected by Global Interactive is used to help diagnose problems with its server and to administer its Web site. User IP address is also used for broad demographic information gathering. All Web user data obtained by Global Interactive is used on an aggregate basis and is in no way personally identifiable. 

Advertisers using the Global Interactive services are connected to our network of downstream partner sites that may distribute their ads. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads may be collected by our own company or our advertisers. Advertisers may employ third-party service providers that collect anonymous user visit information such as user IP address, visited URL, banner shown, pre-existing cookie and date/time of user’s visit. Global Interactive cannot be held responsible for the actions of third parties or their privacy practices as Global Interactive has no control over the information collected.

  3. **Members/Clients**  
Our members and clients may be asked to submit personally identifiable information that may include their contact information (i.e. - name, postal address), unique identifiers (i.e. - social security number), and demographic information (i.e. - zip code, age, income level). Global Interactive treats all personal information collected from its clients and members as completely confidential.
  4. **Security**  
Every precaution is taken to ensure that all personal information is properly protected and is kept secure against misuse, improper modification, or loss. All collected personal information that is stored on Global Interactive's servers is regarded as confidential and is not made available to the outside public. Access to all personally identifiable information is password protected. Global Interactive employs internal security policy with regard to collected personal information whereby access to such information may be given to its employees or third parties on a need-to-know basis to ensure effective delivery of Global Interactive products and services.
  5. **Demographic and Profile Data**  
This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. Gathered data is used to enhance user visits to sites within our network by providing relevant content that will most likely suit the user's needs. All efforts are made to display content according to our users' preferences.
  6. **Special Offers**  
Global Interactive uses its member and client email lists for administrative purposes. Members/Clients receive a welcome e-mail containing their login information and instructions. Members/Clients may receive emails with promotions and other special offers offered by the network.
  7. **Surveys**  
Online surveys run by Global Interactive may ask visitors for contact information (i.e. - email address). Global Interactive reserves the right to use all contact information obtained from the surveys to get in touch with the visitor when necessary.
  8. **External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. Global Interactive is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
  9. **Liability Limitation, Third Party Information & Language**  
YOU AGREE THAT GLOBAL INTERACTIVE’S LIABILITY FOR BREACHING THIS PRIVACY POLICY SHALL BE LIMITED TO THE NET VALUE OF SERVICES PROVIDED TO YOU BY GLOBAL INTERACTIVE TO THE EXTENT SUCH CLAIM IS NOT OTHERWISE BARRED BY GLOBAL INTERACTIVE’S TERMS AND CONDITIONS. YOU ALSO AGREE THAT ANY PRIVACY RELATED DISPUTE WILL BE SUBJECT TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND APPLICABLE TERMS AND CONDITIONS AND POLICIES (INCLUDING LIMITATIONS ON DAMAGES, AND ARBITRATION OF DISPUTES). 

You also agree that any third party individuals whose personal data you provide to Global Interactive have been notified and granted you their complete consent regarding: (1) which set of third party data is required and which, if any, is optional; (2) the intentions and purposes for collecting the personal data; (3) the recipients or intended recipients of the third party’s personal data; and (4) the third party’s ability to access and, if necessary, change the data stored about them. 

All parties have consented for this agreement and all documents relating to this agreement to be drawn up in English. C'est la volonté expresse des parties que la présente convention ainsi que les documents qui s'y rattachent soient rédigés en anglais.

  10. **Notification of Changes**  
In the event that our privacy policy is changed, all changes will be posted on this current page so that the user is aware of our information gathering, storing and disseminating practices. In case the policy is changed, all information will be used in accordance with the privacy policy under which it was collected.
  11. **Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you may use the following contact information to get in touch with us by e-mail: [privacy@globalinteractive.com](mailto:privacy@globalinteractive.com)
, or by postal mail: 

Global Interactive, LLC  
Privacy Officer  
840 East 8th Street, STE 4N  
Brooklyn, NY 11230  
U.S.A 

---|---
